{
    "subject": "resource/Adolph_Menzel",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Artist",
    "human_readable": "Adolph Menzel is an Artist.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9718732237815857,
            "question": "Is Adolph Menzel considered a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8726630806922913,
            "question": "Who was Adolph Menzel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8188883066177368,
            "question": "Is Adolph Menzel a famous writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7085701823234558,
            "question": "Was Adolph Menzel an architect?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7075406908988953,
            "question": "What profession was Adolph Menzel known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6864470839500427,
            "question": "Adolph Menzel was primarily known for his skills in what area?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.679253101348877,
            "question": "Adolph Menzel worked in which creative field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6391327381134033,
            "question": "What is the name of Adolph Menzel's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5321844816207886,
            "question": "What type of work is Adolph Menzel associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20260177552700043,
            "question": "In what field did Adolph Menzel excel?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Adolph Menzel is an Artist.",
            "html": "dbpedia_666_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work is Adolph Menzel associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_666_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Adolph Menzel's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_666_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Adolph Menzel worked in which creative field?",
            "html": "dbpedia_666_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_666_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_666_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_666_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_666_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_666_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_666_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_666_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_666_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_666_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_666_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Adolph Menzel is an Artist\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents all describe Adolph Menzel as a German artist, renowned for his drawings, etchings, and paintings, and one of the most prominent artists of his time in Germany. This suggests that he is indeed an artist, and therefore the triple is supported by the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Adolph Menzel's profession, stating he was a German artist renowned for his drawings, etchings, and paintings. Therefore, the statement \"Adolph Menzel is an Artist\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}